question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In 'Overwatch', an allied McCree will say 'Step right up' upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The card game 'Munchkin' won the 2001 Origins Award for Best Traditional Card Game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "'Mongolia' was a part of the now non-existent U.S.S.R.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "A Millinillion is a real number.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney's film Fantasia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "You can tell the age of a ladybird by counting the spots on his back.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
